

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programing Language: PHP, SQL, Node.js
- Rest API Development,
- Laravel Framewok
- Object Oriented Programming

LET'S CHAT:

+62 881-8354-853 Bandung, West Java, Indonesia 40191 rivannurdin001@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/rivanuwo Instagram: @rivanuwo

REFERENCES:

Zapra Leader Team +62 812-2016-885 zapra@gmail.com

Ridho Cahyo Utomo CEO Exaditama Teknologi Kreativa +62 822-1419-9074 ridho.cahyo.utomo@gmail.com

Rivan Nurdin

Back End Developer

An ordinary human who happens to be destined to become a Backend Developer in 2017 until now. Experiencedin building Management API in the information technology industry for 3 years using the PHP and SQLprogramming languages with Laravel Framework. And now I focus on the Node.js programming language.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Back End Developer

PT HEXA MAJU SAMASTA NOV 2019 - PRESENT

- Make a plan or design a program before wiring a program
- Search and analyst bugs in the program
- Test the program on the websites so that it is feasible to the run

Back End Developer

PT EXADITAMA TEKNOLOGI KREATIVA MAY 2019 - NOV 2019

- Make a plan or design a program before wiring a program
- Search and analyze bugs in the program
- Test the program on the websites so that it is feasible to the run

Junior Web Developer

PT EXA ADITAMA INTERNASIONAL JUN 2017 - DES 2018

- Work with the senior team
- Responsible for basic code generation
- Streamline the entire development process

EDUCATIONAL INFO

Informatics Engineering

ARS UNIVERSITY

Expected graduation date: May 2023

Departement Of Software Engineering

VOCATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL PELITA BANDUNG

Graduated In 2017